{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200528864","data":{"timestamp":" 948200528863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_ivo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200538525","data":{"timestamp":" 948200538525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_eka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200546642","data":{"timestamp":" 948200546642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_eka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200555155","data":{"timestamp":" 948200555155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_eka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200568046","data":{"timestamp":" 948200568046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b_nti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200579393","data":{"timestamp":" 948200579393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_izi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200596184","data":{"timestamp":" 948200596183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200606234","data":{"timestamp":" 948200606234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p_ke"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200626630","data":{"timestamp":" 948200626630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_cho"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200633743","data":{"timestamp":" 948200633742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_cho"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200642033","data":{"timestamp":" 948200642033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_cho"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200649465","data":{"timestamp":" 948200649465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_cho"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200663217","data":{"timestamp":" 948200663217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_cho"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200673603","data":{"timestamp":" 948200673603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e_yi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200687569","data":{"timestamp":" 948200687568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_s_pu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200700959","data":{"timestamp":" 948200700959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200713797","data":{"timestamp":" 948200713795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 25fd8108-f18e-4346-b8f6-1a7bb1c629ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_n_e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200748204","data":{"timestamp":" 948200748204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ongo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200754593","data":{"timestamp":" 948200754593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ongo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200764223","data":{"timestamp":" 948200764223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__witu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200773248","data":{"timestamp":" 948200773248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__tamu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200781724","data":{"timestamp":" 948200781724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iji"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200797707","data":{"timestamp":" 948200797706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__umu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200816258","data":{"timestamp":" 948200816258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__unde"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200824955","data":{"timestamp":" 948200824955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200848452","data":{"timestamp":" 948200848452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200868155","data":{"timestamp":" 948200868155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200878258","data":{"timestamp":" 948200878258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__acho"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200887208","data":{"timestamp":" 948200887208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ije"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200904909","data":{"timestamp":" 948200904909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__vuto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.6.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200918382","data":{"timestamp":" 948200918381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" b8a59be5-34f6-424b-b739-ba8163ec42b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.6.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write__vuto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200951281","data":{"timestamp":" 948200951280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" START_MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200952964","data":{"timestamp":" 948200952963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200957445","data":{"timestamp":" 948200957444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200958886","data":{"timestamp":" 948200958885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" START_NINAPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200960683","data":{"timestamp":" 948200960682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200961945","data":{"timestamp":" 948200961944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200965616","data":{"timestamp":" 948200965615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200967535","data":{"timestamp":" 948200967535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200969376","data":{"timestamp":" 948200969375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200970646","data":{"timestamp":" 948200970645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200976248","data":{"timestamp":" 948200976248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LESIBA"," userResponse":" LESIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200977367","data":{"timestamp":" 948200977367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" START_AMELALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200978890","data":{"timestamp":" 948200978890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200980492","data":{"timestamp":" 948200980491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200984361","data":{"timestamp":" 948200984361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200986231","data":{"timestamp":" 948200986230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200987304","data":{"timestamp":" 948200987303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200989981","data":{"timestamp":" 948200989981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200990390","data":{"timestamp":" 948200990389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200990769","data":{"timestamp":" 948200990769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200991484","data":{"timestamp":" 948200991483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPIKA"," userResponse":" WANAPIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200993165","data":{"timestamp":" 948200993164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200994949","data":{"timestamp":" 948200994949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200996555","data":{"timestamp":" 948200996554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200997497","data":{"timestamp":" 948200997496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200997879","data":{"timestamp":" 948200997879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200998587","data":{"timestamp":" 948200998586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948200999385","data":{"timestamp":" 948200999384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" START_WANAREKEBISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201000350","data":{"timestamp":" 948201000350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANAREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201002383","data":{"timestamp":" 948201002382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201003762","data":{"timestamp":" 948201003761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201005254","data":{"timestamp":" 948201005253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201010439","data":{"timestamp":" 948201010439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201010941","data":{"timestamp":" 948201010941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201012952","data":{"timestamp":" 948201012952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201014421","data":{"timestamp":" 948201014421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" START_NAWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201015971","data":{"timestamp":" 948201015971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201017244","data":{"timestamp":" 948201017244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201017350","data":{"timestamp":" 948201017350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201018280","data":{"timestamp":" 948201018279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201018870","data":{"timestamp":" 948201018870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" START_KUKIFURAHIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201020525","data":{"timestamp":" 948201020525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" START_KUKIFURAHIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201022392","data":{"timestamp":" 948201022392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201023368","data":{"timestamp":" 948201023367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" START_KITABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201024990","data":{"timestamp":" 948201024990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201025884","data":{"timestamp":" 948201025884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201027092","data":{"timestamp":" 948201027092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201029118","data":{"timestamp":" 948201029117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201029284","data":{"timestamp":" 948201029284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 800d7833-bcc7-412f-a408-2fb34f663a10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201042727","data":{"timestamp":" 948201042727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201054616","data":{"timestamp":" 948201054616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201054620","data":{"timestamp":" 948201054620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201056259","data":{"timestamp":" 948201056258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" START_ANALIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201058068","data":{"timestamp":" 948201058068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" ANALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201061783","data":{"timestamp":" 948201061782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201062396","data":{"timestamp":" 948201062395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" START_ANAHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201063333","data":{"timestamp":" 948201063333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201064619","data":{"timestamp":" 948201064619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201068697","data":{"timestamp":" 948201068697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201068706","data":{"timestamp":" 948201068706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201069242","data":{"timestamp":" 948201069242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201070406","data":{"timestamp":" 948201070406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201072168","data":{"timestamp":" 948201072167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201073327","data":{"timestamp":" 948201073326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" START_AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201074326","data":{"timestamp":" 948201074326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201076254","data":{"timestamp":" 948201076254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201081432","data":{"timestamp":" 948201081431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" START_NADHANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201083490","data":{"timestamp":" 948201083490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201085781","data":{"timestamp":" 948201085780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201086823","data":{"timestamp":" 948201086823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201088779","data":{"timestamp":" 948201088778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201089859","data":{"timestamp":" 948201089858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201090227","data":{"timestamp":" 948201090227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201093199","data":{"timestamp":" 948201093199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201093210","data":{"timestamp":" 948201093209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201095209","data":{"timestamp":" 948201095209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201096378","data":{"timestamp":" 948201096378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" START_AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201097215","data":{"timestamp":" 948201097214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201099230","data":{"timestamp":" 948201099229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201101671","data":{"timestamp":" 948201101671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201102397","data":{"timestamp":" 948201102397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201102784","data":{"timestamp":" 948201102784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201103955","data":{"timestamp":" 948201103955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201104467","data":{"timestamp":" 948201104467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201105878","data":{"timestamp":" 948201105877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201109190","data":{"timestamp":" 948201109189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201111490","data":{"timestamp":" 948201111490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201114312","data":{"timestamp":" 948201114312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" START_ANACHEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201115802","data":{"timestamp":" 948201115802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" ANACHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201118271","data":{"timestamp":" 948201118270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201121259","data":{"timestamp":" 948201121259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201122185","data":{"timestamp":" 948201122184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201123079","data":{"timestamp":" 948201123079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201124889","data":{"timestamp":" 948201124888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201125814","data":{"timestamp":" 948201125814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201130299","data":{"timestamp":" 948201130299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201132834","data":{"timestamp":" 948201132834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201138190","data":{"timestamp":" 948201138190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201139429","data":{"timestamp":" 948201139429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201141199","data":{"timestamp":" 948201141199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" START_WANASOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201143211","data":{"timestamp":" 948201143211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" WANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201144709","data":{"timestamp":" 948201144708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201145216","data":{"timestamp":" 948201145216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201150033","data":{"timestamp":" 948201150033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201152065","data":{"timestamp":" 948201152065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201153076","data":{"timestamp":" 948201153075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201155475","data":{"timestamp":" 948201155475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201158991","data":{"timestamp":" 948201158990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201160395","data":{"timestamp":" 948201160395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201161416","data":{"timestamp":" 948201161416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201162892","data":{"timestamp":" 948201162891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201167737","data":{"timestamp":" 948201167736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201170750","data":{"timestamp":" 948201170750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" ANAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201173432","data":{"timestamp":" 948201173432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201175443","data":{"timestamp":" 948201175442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201175658","data":{"timestamp":" 948201175657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201187886","data":{"timestamp":" 948201187886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 1f353dab-475b-4bf7-b957-78d47408afea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201201243","data":{"timestamp":" 948201201242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201202139","data":{"timestamp":" 948201202138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201202149","data":{"timestamp":" 948201202149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201202161","data":{"timestamp":" 948201202160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201202834","data":{"timestamp":" 948201202834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201205844","data":{"timestamp":" 948201205844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201206566","data":{"timestamp":" 948201206566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201207162","data":{"timestamp":" 948201207161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201207864","data":{"timestamp":" 948201207864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201208349","data":{"timestamp":" 948201208349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201211221","data":{"timestamp":" 948201211220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201211632","data":{"timestamp":" 948201211631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" START_AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201212854","data":{"timestamp":" 948201212854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" START_AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201214741","data":{"timestamp":" 948201214740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201214892","data":{"timestamp":" 948201214891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201215049","data":{"timestamp":" 948201215049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" START_AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201216057","data":{"timestamp":" 948201216057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201217410","data":{"timestamp":" 948201217410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201217722","data":{"timestamp":" 948201217721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201218530","data":{"timestamp":" 948201218530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201220286","data":{"timestamp":" 948201220285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201220653","data":{"timestamp":" 948201220653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201224948","data":{"timestamp":" 948201224948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201225650","data":{"timestamp":" 948201225650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201226353","data":{"timestamp":" 948201226353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201228225","data":{"timestamp":" 948201228224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201231602","data":{"timestamp":" 948201231602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201232020","data":{"timestamp":" 948201232019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" START_ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201233771","data":{"timestamp":" 948201233770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" START_ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201235539","data":{"timestamp":" 948201235539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201236623","data":{"timestamp":" 948201236623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201236923","data":{"timestamp":" 948201236922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201240726","data":{"timestamp":" 948201240726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201243435","data":{"timestamp":" 948201243435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201244769","data":{"timestamp":" 948201244768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201246603","data":{"timestamp":" 948201246603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201247913","data":{"timestamp":" 948201247912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201251408","data":{"timestamp":" 948201251407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201254926","data":{"timestamp":" 948201254925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" START_ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201257989","data":{"timestamp":" 948201257988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" START_ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201259775","data":{"timestamp":" 948201259774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201261543","data":{"timestamp":" 948201261543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201264508","data":{"timestamp":" 948201264508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201265598","data":{"timestamp":" 948201265598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201266312","data":{"timestamp":" 948201266312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201266718","data":{"timestamp":" 948201266718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201269607","data":{"timestamp":" 948201269607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201270005","data":{"timestamp":" 948201270005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201270686","data":{"timestamp":" 948201270686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201272405","data":{"timestamp":" 948201272404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201273303","data":{"timestamp":" 948201273302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALALA"," userResponse":" ANALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201275688","data":{"timestamp":" 948201275688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201276494","data":{"timestamp":" 948201276493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201278064","data":{"timestamp":" 948201278063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201280220","data":{"timestamp":" 948201280219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201281488","data":{"timestamp":" 948201281488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201285174","data":{"timestamp":" 948201285173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201285700","data":{"timestamp":" 948201285700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" START_ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201296523","data":{"timestamp":" 948201296523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201298557","data":{"timestamp":" 948201298556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201298779","data":{"timestamp":" 948201298779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 51630760-7a3e-41bd-9360-6175261ddc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201321865","data":{"timestamp":" 948201321864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" de9ecb00-659d-4dc8-8eb3-33ad4e45c8df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201324436","data":{"timestamp":" 948201324436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" de9ecb00-659d-4dc8-8eb3-33ad4e45c8df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201326564","data":{"timestamp":" 948201326563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" de9ecb00-659d-4dc8-8eb3-33ad4e45c8df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201326768","data":{"timestamp":" 948201326767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" de9ecb00-659d-4dc8-8eb3-33ad4e45c8df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201326933","data":{"timestamp":" 948201326933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" de9ecb00-659d-4dc8-8eb3-33ad4e45c8df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201342122","data":{"timestamp":" 948201342122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201343865","data":{"timestamp":" 948201343864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201345542","data":{"timestamp":" 948201345542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201346960","data":{"timestamp":" 948201346960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201348689","data":{"timestamp":" 948201348688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201355560","data":{"timestamp":" 948201355559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201357276","data":{"timestamp":" 948201357276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201359360","data":{"timestamp":" 948201359360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201361869","data":{"timestamp":" 948201361869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201361882","data":{"timestamp":" 948201361882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201365409","data":{"timestamp":" 948201365409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201366609","data":{"timestamp":" 948201366609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201371165","data":{"timestamp":" 948201371164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201373903","data":{"timestamp":" 948201373903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201380198","data":{"timestamp":" 948201380198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201380208","data":{"timestamp":" 948201380207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201383431","data":{"timestamp":" 948201383430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" START_KIMYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201384920","data":{"timestamp":" 948201384919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201386489","data":{"timestamp":" 948201386488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201391121","data":{"timestamp":" 948201391121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201392538","data":{"timestamp":" 948201392537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201392548","data":{"timestamp":" 948201392548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201394330","data":{"timestamp":" 948201394329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201394937","data":{"timestamp":" 948201394936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201395245","data":{"timestamp":" 948201395244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201396223","data":{"timestamp":" 948201396222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201396636","data":{"timestamp":" 948201396636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" START_ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201397596","data":{"timestamp":" 948201397595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201399420","data":{"timestamp":" 948201399420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201401184","data":{"timestamp":" 948201401184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201402636","data":{"timestamp":" 948201402635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201403881","data":{"timestamp":" 948201403880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201405748","data":{"timestamp":" 948201405747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201407022","data":{"timestamp":" 948201407022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201408127","data":{"timestamp":" 948201408127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201410162","data":{"timestamp":" 948201410160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201410324","data":{"timestamp":" 948201410324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201425162","data":{"timestamp":" 948201425162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 8300845e-64be-4508-b2d6-c8bd3445a84a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201443178","data":{"timestamp":" 948201443178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201447098","data":{"timestamp":" 948201447097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201447357","data":{"timestamp":" 948201447357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201447798","data":{"timestamp":" 948201447797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201452690","data":{"timestamp":" 948201452689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201455848","data":{"timestamp":" 948201455847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARIFIKI"," userResponse":" WANNE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201459247","data":{"timestamp":" 948201459246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIFIKI"," userResponse":" MARIFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201459256","data":{"timestamp":" 948201459255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANNE"," userResponse":" WANNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201462602","data":{"timestamp":" 948201462602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201464391","data":{"timestamp":" 948201464390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201466343","data":{"timestamp":" 948201466342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201468695","data":{"timestamp":" 948201468694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201475529","data":{"timestamp":" 948201475529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201481665","data":{"timestamp":" 948201481665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201483822","data":{"timestamp":" 948201483822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201483978","data":{"timestamp":" 948201483978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201484280","data":{"timestamp":" 948201484279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201487179","data":{"timestamp":" 948201487179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201489364","data":{"timestamp":" 948201489363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201495639","data":{"timestamp":" 948201495638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201498811","data":{"timestamp":" 948201498810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201498822","data":{"timestamp":" 948201498822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201498833","data":{"timestamp":" 948201498833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201501800","data":{"timestamp":" 948201501799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201503845","data":{"timestamp":" 948201503844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201508878","data":{"timestamp":" 948201508878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201514055","data":{"timestamp":" 948201514055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201516761","data":{"timestamp":" 948201516760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201519303","data":{"timestamp":" 948201519303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFICHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201522494","data":{"timestamp":" 948201522492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201525143","data":{"timestamp":" 948201525143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201527778","data":{"timestamp":" 948201527778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AYANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201531354","data":{"timestamp":" 948201531354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201533683","data":{"timestamp":" 948201533682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201537910","data":{"timestamp":" 948201537909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201540097","data":{"timestamp":" 948201540097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201543918","data":{"timestamp":" 948201543918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201546681","data":{"timestamp":" 948201546680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201548162","data":{"timestamp":" 948201548161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAVYOPENDA"," userResponse":" START_WANAVYOPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201549472","data":{"timestamp":" 948201549471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANAVYOPENDA"," userResponse":" START_WANAVYOPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201551395","data":{"timestamp":" 948201551394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAVYOPENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201553966","data":{"timestamp":" 948201553966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" WANAVYOPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201559812","data":{"timestamp":" 948201559812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" WANAVYOPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201561563","data":{"timestamp":" 948201561562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201563932","data":{"timestamp":" 948201563931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NACHEZA"," userResponse":" NACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201564419","data":{"timestamp":" 948201564418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201564611","data":{"timestamp":" 948201564611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201565117","data":{"timestamp":" 948201565116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" ZIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201569109","data":{"timestamp":" 948201569109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201572913","data":{"timestamp":" 948201572913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" BWAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201574263","data":{"timestamp":" 948201574263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201577652","data":{"timestamp":" 948201577651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201579763","data":{"timestamp":" 948201579763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201583245","data":{"timestamp":" 948201583245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201585518","data":{"timestamp":" 948201585517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NACHEZA"," userResponse":" NACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201585976","data":{"timestamp":" 948201585976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" START_MCHEZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201587086","data":{"timestamp":" 948201587086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201587098","data":{"timestamp":" 948201587097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201587870","data":{"timestamp":" 948201587870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFICHA"," userResponse":" START_KUJIFICHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201591406","data":{"timestamp":" 948201591406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFICHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201593533","data":{"timestamp":" 948201593533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201595209","data":{"timestamp":" 948201595209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201597495","data":{"timestamp":" 948201597495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201603189","data":{"timestamp":" 948201603189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201605397","data":{"timestamp":" 948201605397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201605706","data":{"timestamp":" 948201605705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201606782","data":{"timestamp":" 948201606781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201611371","data":{"timestamp":" 948201611370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201614160","data":{"timestamp":" 948201614160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201616289","data":{"timestamp":" 948201616289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201618330","data":{"timestamp":" 948201618330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201621083","data":{"timestamp":" 948201621082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201623103","data":{"timestamp":" 948201623103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201625119","data":{"timestamp":" 948201625119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948201625272","data":{"timestamp":" 948201625272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000118_160136"," gameId":" 65081197-7d4a-47ea-9fe5-49ac9299b1b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}